JACKEY WILSON GEORGE

Email id: jackey.wilson@gmail.com

Mob No.: +91 999 800 7773



MY OBJECTIVE

To work in a technically developed environment to enhance my managerial capabilities (MBA in Marketing & Retail Management with 5 years' experience), simultaneously climbing up the hierarchy in the organization and contributing to achieve the organizational goals and objective. A reputed position in the Marketing, Administration or Retail Industry which exploits my talents and empowers me to explore new avenues to learn and perform with utmost efficiency and competence.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

M/s ORIENTAL TIRE WORKS, Nadiad, India

Period: February 2016 to date Designation: Relationship Manager

- Providing with Marketing and Service Solution for Tire and Tubes.
- Providing customers with available best variants suiting their vehicular requirement.
- Compliance with systems and procedures.
- Sourcing of new clients and new assignments

M/s RAKBANK, Dubai, UAE

Period: September 2015 to January 2016 Designation: Relationship Officer

- Providing with business liabilities products suitable for the SME in UAE.
- Providing customers with available best options suiting their requirement.
- Compliance with systems and procedures.
- Sourcing of new accounts and funding of existing accounts.

M/s VODAFONE INDIA SERVICES Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad, India

Period: September 2011 to February 2015

Designation: Jr. Executive

- Customer grievance handling.
- Giving solutions to the problems customer has with the line or contract connection.
- Providing customers with available offers.
- Compliance with systems and procedures.
- Sourcing of new accounts and funding of existing accounts.
- Helping customers get connected to the correct department as per the requirement.

M/s KOTAK MAHINDRA BANK, Nadiad, India

Period: May 2011 to September 2011 Designation: Asst. Sales Manager

- Customer grievance handling
- Conducted Programmes during Navratri celebration and Womens day celebration.
- Conducted competitions for Childrens' day celebrations.

- Handled Clearing Department: attending clearing house and processing settlement entries, managing current account with other banks.
- Compliance with systems and procedures
- Sourcing of new accounts and funding of existing accounts.
- Have experience in handling banking operations such as transfer of funds, cash transactions.

M/s ADITYA BIRLA MONEY Ltd, Ahmedabad, India

Period: March 2011 to May 2011

Designation: Summer Internship, Management Trainee

- Participated in the Business Development process at ABML.
- Prepared a report on various competitor companies in Nadiad Region and their market share.
- Researching on various products available with other competitor companies
- Maintenance of customer's trade file.

M/s CANAN INFOSYS Pvt. Ltd. Anand, India

Period: April 2008 to April 2011

Part time with studies

- Participated in the Business Development process.
- Sourcing New work Assignments.
- Meeting clients for existing and new assignments in and around Anand District
- Getting the assignments completed on time as per the client requirements.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Won prizes in Inter School competitions for Business Quiz.
- Won prizes in Inter Collegiate Competitions for Management Games.
- Raised funds for Samanvay, a commerce fest organized by DDIBA College.
- Member of Organizing Committee Blood Donation Camps in the college campus.
- Member of Organizing Committee of KSMCS, 2011, a Management Fest and Job Fair organized by K. P. Patel School of Management and Computer Studies.
 - Raised funds for Various Functions in the years 2009-2011
 - Participated in Arohan at NICM, Gandhinagar.
 - Participated in Rural Development Camp at Katlal, Gujarat.
 - Interacted with many prominent managers of the Business World.
 - Industrial visits to Zydus Cadila, Electrotherm, Milcent Appliances Pvt Ltd and Cocacola.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- MBA (Master of Business Administration) (2009 11 Batch) Specialization in Marketing and Retail Gujarat Technological University, K. P. Patel School of Management and Computer Studies, Gujarat
- **BBA (Bachelor of Business Administration)** (DD University) Dharmsinh Desai Institute of Business Administration, Nadiad, Gujarat
- Senior Secondary School (GHSED)
 Gujarat Refinery English Medium School, Vadodara, Gujarat
- Secondary School (GSEB)
 St. Anne's High School, Nadiad, Gujarat

COMPUTER EXPOSURE

Fully literate in Windows 10 based software; in addition to have extensive knowledge to operate all computers related hardware i.e., Input and Output devices. Especially have hands-on practice and presentation through special tools such as:

- Tally ERP9; Microsoft Word; Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Access; Microsoft PowerPoint

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Capable of managing project independently.
- Strong believer of achieving results through Communication and Experience.
- Responsive to change and amiable with colleagues in environments requiring attention.
- Capable of working under pressure.
- Ability to initiate actions & perform critical tasks effectively and timely.
- Committed to continual learning & skill development with knowledge on cutting edge advancement in field.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 25th June, 1989

Sex : Male Marital Status : Single

Permanent Address : 5, Subhalaxmi Society,

Opp. S.R.P Camp,

Kapadwanj Road, Nadiad

Gujarat State - 387001, INDIA

Languages Known : English, Hindi, Malayalam, and Gujarati

Hobbies : Listening to Music, Driving

Passport No. : K7747737 valid up to 11-10-2022

IELTS Band Score : Overall 7 Bands

I hereby declare that the information provided herein is fully accurate and true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

JACKEY WILSON GEORGE